WHO NEEDS FORGIVENESS?
Ask your neighbour.
Hallelujah!
This will take you to the Book of Romans 3 and we will read the proof text verse 23 and also verse 10.
"As it is written: 'There is no one righteous, not even one'."
So I'm taking you to verse 23.
"For all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God."
Hallelujah!
The question remains: Who needs forgiveness?
From the Book of Romans 3:23, one thing is clear - all have sinned.
In verse 10, "There is no one righteous, not even one".
What does this mean?
Whether victims or perpetrators, we all stand in helpless need of His divine forgiveness.
Whether you are the one who caused the trouble or pain
or you are the one who suffered the effects, we all need forgiveness.
Whether you are the one who caused the pain, the trouble
or you are the one who suffers the effects, we all need forgiveness
Take note of that.
Let me also take you to the Book of Luke23:34.
"Jesus said, 'Father, forgive them...' "
Take note of the word 'them'
because it includes both the offender and the offended.
"Father, forgive them." Take note of the word 'them.'
This should be the standard of a Christian.
Tell your neighbour, "This should be your standard".
This should be the standard of a true Christian.
And this should be your standard, if you are a true Christian.
This should be your standard.
He said, "Father forgive them."
Take note of the word 'them'
because it includes both the offender and the offended.
Sin's power over me is broken
Come on!
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
Listen to that!
This should be the standard of a true Christian
because it includes both the offender and the offended.
Sin is never covered by our appearance.
Sin is never covered by our presence.
Nowadays when we come out as ministers of God, we put on a very big chain, this.
This cannot cover our sin.
Sin is never covered by our big Bible.
Some will carry their Bible with two hands.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Sin is never covered by our prayer.
"In Jesus' name..." - no matter how much you pray or tears,
sin can only be removed by repentance.
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
What is repentance?
Repentance means being sorry for sin or wrong; it's not by tears.
It's being sorry for wrong, for sin, being committed to a new way of life, that of serving God.
Repentance comes when we stop blaming others.
When things go wrong, you look around and say,
"Oh, my business is down as a result of witches and wizards.
Ah, that grandmum, grandfather, done this, done that".
We begin to look, pointing our finger at others; looking for a scapegoat.
But when business is booming, it's our handwork.
"I don't sleep, I work throughout the night; as a result, I become a millionaire."
But a poor man will not say, "As a result of my effort, I became poor",
but a rich man - as a result of what?
I trust you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When things are not going well, we point accusing fingers at others.
Tell your neighbour, "Stop repeating stories of those who fail you.
Stop repeating stories of those who hurt you".
Stop repeating stories of those who fail you, who hurt you, who lie against you.
Stop repeating. That will not help you.
Your repentance does not agree with this.
Stop pointing your fingers at others.
"Yes, my boss sacked me, that is why I'm poor.
I don't know what I have done to my boss."
Stop thinking on your flaws, your trouble.
When we are offended, we feel hurt and blame our offender.
We always defend our envy, jealousy, anger, grudges.
We always defend to justify our reason not to forgive.
"No, I will not forgive because he is a small boy, he is my servant."
"No no, it's not possible for me."
We justify our reason not to forgive.
Message Title:
WHO NEEDS FORGIVENESS?
"No no, I'm older than him."
"I helped him. I sent him to university."
"Yes, I'm a boss. Why should this happen to me?"
We always defend our reason not to forgive.
Everyone has limitations - everyone.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you cannot forgive yourself, you cannot forgive others.
Since you have not forgiven yourself, you cannot forgive others.
You need to forgive yourself first, to forgive others. You have not yet forgiven yourself.
So where are we going? Vanity upon vanity.
Stop repeating stories of those who failed you.
Your junior ones, your this, your husband, your wife, your this, your that - stop repeating.
If you don't stop repeating, you will continue to have carryovers in your life.
And that is what is happening to you now.
Tell your neighbour, "You have carryovers".
'Carryover' means the trouble you had yesterday, you are still experiencing it.
The trouble last week, you are still in it. That is 'carryover'.
When you have carryovers, you cannot enjoy today's grace.
You know in your university days - 'carryover', you know what it means.
You study with your mate, you go back to your junior too, you study with them.
You go back again to your first year; you go back to the junior class to study.
When you are studying now, they don't know whether you are a senior or a junior.
What a humiliation.
You are living a carryover life because you keep repeating the stories of those who failed you,
stories of those who hurt you.
That is the life you are living now - carryover.
You carry the trouble yesterday and carry the trouble today and you are not destined like that.
You are only destined to face the trouble today.
The grace today is for today.
You carry yesterday's trouble and carry today's trouble.
Today's grace is for today.
This is the case with you.
You heard what Jesus said; I repeat again.
He said, "Father forgive them".
Take note of the word 'them'.
The word 'them' means the offender and the offended,
the one that caused the trouble and also the one that suffered the effects.
I want to pray with you. Thank you.
This is for you so that you will be able to maintain your blessing.
You just have to live and let others live.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
Sin's power over me is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Don't be a man of prayer but perhaps not a man of faith.
Tell your neighbour.
[Don't be a man of prayer but perhaps not a man of faith.]
I can't hear you.
Because when we say, "Let's pray...",
it is faith that counts.
All this "Jesus!" without faith, you are talking to yourself.
Tell your neighbour, "Don't be a man of prayer but perhaps not a man of faith".
I can't hear you.
[Don't be a man of prayer but perhaps not a man of faith.]
Yes!
It is faith that counts!
All this praying, "In the name of Jesus!" -
that is why you cannot give account of your prayer.
Don't be a man of prayer but perhaps not a man of faith, because it is faith that counts.
Viewers all over the world, listen to me.
I will not pray with you if I am not receiving an order.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Sin must be brought to the Blood of Jesus before the Spirit prays through us.
Are you with me?
The Blood of Jesus
The Blood of Jesus sets me free
From sin and sorrow
The Blood of Jesus
The Blood of Jesus sets me free
From sin and sorrow
Do you understand what I'm saying now?
You are the one singing it but you don't know what you are saying.
Our sin must be brought to the Blood of Christ before the Spirit prays through us.
This is where faith counts.
Be released, in the name of Jesus, from all hurt, deep hurt, envy, jealousy, anger.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus, from all hurt, deep hurt, anger, envy, jealousy!
In the name of Jesus!
If are not be released from all this and we are praying,
you can receive but it will not be permanent.
You can receive a miracle but to keep that miracle, you must be a member of Christ's home.
Be released, in the name of Jesus, from all hurt, deep hurt, anger, bitterness, envy, jealousy!
In the name of Jesus!
Right now, open your lips and begin to release yourself from all hurt, deep hurt, anger,
bitterness, envy, jealousy.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Those who are under the bondage and dominion of the devil - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Those who are under the bondage and dominion of satan, in whatever way,
be released, in the name of Jesus!
I can see God's deliverance touching you -
touching your life, career, finances, business, family!
Agree with me - I can feel God's deliverance touching me!
Confess this!
I see the Cherubim moving round.
I see the Cherubim moving round, touching you!
Someone is touching you in the Person of the Holy Ghost.
Someone is touching you, Someone is moving round in the Person of the Holy Ghost.
Someone is working, Someone is touching you, touching your career,
touching your business, touching your family, touching your health,
touching your marriage, touching your finances.
Someone is touching you.
Someone is moving round in the Person of the Holy Ghost.
Holy Ghost!
Viewers at home, viewers all over the world, wherever you are right now -
Someone is touching you in the Person of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Give thanks to Him!
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing on you right now!
I command healing on you now!
I command healing on you!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I command healing on you now!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen to the voice of God! This is for you - get it !
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Prepare your faith!
Healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
I can see God's healing touching you!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
It's broken indeed!
Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Right now, your country, your nation.
Whatever you have with you as a contact point, pray for your nation.
Sin's power over your nation - be broken!
I can't hear you.
[Sin's power over my nation - be broken!]
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
Begin to cover your nation with the Blood of Jesus.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Cover your nation with the Blood of Jesus!
Seal your nation with the Blood of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Right now, your righteous journey -
as you are going, you need the grace of God to continue this journey.
You want to live right, you want to do things right,
you want to say things right -
ask God to give you the grace.
The life you have received today - you want to continue living it.
You don't want to fall back.
You want to continue this life.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Grace!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Ask Him to make you His channel - channel of love out there, channel of faithfulness,
channel of humility, obedience.
Make me Your channel - channel of love!
Make me Your channel - channel of faithfulness!
Make me Your channel - channel of kindness!
Make me Your channel - channel of humility!
Make me Your channel - channel of obedience!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The day you will sing this song in your dream - oh my God.
That is the day you will begin to wine and dine with God.
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
Don't stop singing this song.
As you are looking at me, continue meditating in your heart.
Let it be your prayer. You need to sing it all the time.
The day you will find yourself, your darling, your son,
your daughter say, "Mummy, Mummy, you are singing!"
"I'm singing - which song?"
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
Please continue now as you are talking, you look, as you are walking, you need to sing this song.
You just need that kind of relationship with God.
Issue of prosperity, issue of this, issue of that - no.
The relationship contains all this.
Once you have that relationship, all other things follow.
Prosperity, blessing, breakthrough - you are just asking for a part.
Why can't you ask for the whole?
Sin's power over me is broken
Sin's power over us is broken
When Jesus went I went
When He went we went
Sin's power over us is broken
Let me tell you something - this song is anointed!
You are under His eyes.
TT Monica Asefa 27/04/19
RV: Mel Flowers 01/05/2019